jcs.tokyo 2016-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Japan Content Showcase 2016

  1. __HOME
  2. Privacy Policy

### Treatment of Personal Information

  * 1\. In the event Participant acquires personal information through the exhibition or other situations, Registrants shall observe the Personal Information Protection Law and related laws and regulations. In particular, if Registrants gives personal information to a third party, Registrants shall obtain the consent from the person concerned except as set forth in the 2 under this Article and others. In the event that any dispute arises between Registrants and the person concerned regarding such personal information, both parties shall settle such dispute upon consultation between them and Organizer shall assume no responsibility whatsoever regarding such dispute.
  * 2\. Organizer will properly and safely manage the personal information provided by clients, take steps to prevent leakage, loss or damage of the personal information, endeavor to protect the personal information, establishing treatment thereof as set forth below. Client’s personal information entrusted to us will be used to support mutual business with our industry party for the following purpose, pursuant to the client’s grant: 
    * 1\. To post on “List of Participants” on our official website.
    * 2\. To publish in “List of Participants” in our official guide book.
    * 3\. To publish corporate information and product information in various publications distributed in the exhibition site.
    * 4\. To introduce client when the client appears on our official video or in the market report.
    * 5\. To print client’s name, company name, nationality and face photo on ID badge for Identification.
    * 6\. To deliver various services and information and periodical news by telephone, mail, E-mail, etc.
    * 7\. To study, analyze and plan new product and service we offer, making use of market research, data analysis, questionnaires, etc.
    * 8\. To inform client of oncoming events, symposiums, or seminars.
    * 9\. To identify client, to know about registered information, and to contact and give information to client.
    * 10\. In order for the person of the related events to contact the client for the purpose of market research, data analysis, questionnaires, etc.

However, website related information is disclosed only to client who has ID and password. Client’s personal information shall not be disclosed without the consent of the client, except above items and for the government agency’s legal request for disclosure. In the event of outsourcing the whole or part of the operation, Organizer will establish an administrative system capable of appropriate protection of personal information, conclude a secrecy agreement and strictly control clients’ personal information. Other inquiries regarding treatment of personal information will be received at the contact address set forth in this Rules. Various data that accompany the application for the Exhibition are appropriately protected and controlled by Organizer according to the Organizer’s Privacy Policy.
